pseudo elements there's more to your HTML than meets the eye there are parts
伪元素HTML 的内容远比表面上看到
of the UI that you can style with CSS that don't actually exist in your HTML
的要多 用户界面的某些部分可以使用 CSS 设置样式，但 HTML 标记中实际上并不存在，
markup take for example a form input that has some placeholder text the
例如，表单输入包含一些占位符文本，
placeholder value is defined as an attribute on the element so how do we
占位符值定义为元素上的一个属性那么我们如何
get ahold of the placeholder to style it the answer is we target a pseudo element
获得占位符来设置它的样式答案是我们
in our CSS they always have a double colon to distinguish them from pseudo
在我们的 CSS 中定位一个伪元素它们总是有一个双冒号来区分它们与伪
classes the difference is that a pseudo element represents an actual part of the
类不同的是伪元素代表一个实际
Dom whereas a pseudo class represents the state of an element based on the
Dom 的一部分，而伪类表示基于
user's interaction with it pseudo elements can make your code much more
用户与其交互的元素的状态，伪元素可以使您的代码更加
efficient take for example this HTML where the first letter in each paragraph
高效，例如这个 HTML，其中每个段落中的第一个字母
is being wrapped in a span so it can be styled a far more efficient way to solve
被包装在一个跨度中，所以它 可以设置样式来解决此问题的一种更有效的方法
this problem is by targeting the first letter on the paragraph element the end
是通过定位段落元素上的第一个字母最终
result is much cleaner semantic HTML that's cool but by far the most powerful
结果是更清晰的语义 HTML，这很酷但 到目前为止，最强大的
pseudo elements are before and after many but not all HTML elements can have
伪元素是在许多 HTML 元素之前和之后，但并非所有 HTML 元素都可以
content inserted before or after their inner content handled entirely from your
在其内部内容之前或之后插入内容，这些内容完全由您的
CSS code for example we can target before and provide an empty string as
CSS 代码处理，例如，我们可以定位before 并提供一个空字符串
the content property now that we've targeted this element you'll notice that
作为 content 属性现在 我们已经定位了这个元素你会注意到
it shows up in the browser's inspector we can style this element as if it were
它显示在浏览器的检查器中我们可以为这个元素设置样式，就好像它
an empty span or div in our HTML and that can be very useful for creating
是我们 HTML 中的一个空 span 或 div，这对于创建高级动画非常有用，
advanced animations without polluting your HTML markup imagine we have a big
而不会污染你的 HTML 标记 假设我们有一个很大的
unordered list and before each list item we have an emoji character instead of
无序列表，并且在每个列表项之前我们有一个表情符号字符，而不是
duplicating it in the markup we can simply add it as the content property to
在标记中复制它，我们可以简单地将其作为 content 属性添加
the before selector and once again we're left with code that is far more
到 before 选择器中，我们再次得到更多的代码
maintainable there's a few other pseudo elements that you should know about
可维护的还有一些其他的伪元素，你应该知道
selection allows you to change the background and color of highlighted text
选择允许你改变一些浏览器（如 chrome）中突出显示的文本的背景和颜色，
in some browsers like chrome but not Firefox you can customize the scroll bar
但是 不是Firefox，您可以
on scrollable elements before using the pseudo element always check for browser
在使用伪元素之前自定义可滚动元素上的滚动条始终检查浏览器
compatibility ones like spelling error might sound cool but they don't really
兼容性 诸如拼写错误之类的可能听起来很酷，但它们实际上
have any browser support yet this has been pseudo elements in 100 seconds make
并没有任何浏览器支持，但这已经是 100 秒内的伪元素
sure to also check out pseudo classes thanks for watching and I will see you
确保 还可以查看伪类感谢收看，我会
in the next one you
在下一个你看到你